

7+ years of design experience with programming experience using JavaScript, HTML, and CSS, specializing in building scalable front-end products with great user experiences. I am currently looking for a hybrid UI/UX designer position to support between design and development.

### **PORTFOLIO**

Link https://tinyurl.com/yuzcajzk

Website jaykim-dev.netlify.app

# **CONTACT**

**Phone** +1 (469) 386-6307

Email develop.jay8675@gmail.com

Address Dallas, Texas

# **SOCIAL**

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/jay8675

Github github.com/jaehyung8675

# **SKILLS**

**Design** User Experience (UX)

User Interface (UI)

Product Graphic Visual

**Programming** JavaScript

React HTML5 Sass / SCSS

CSS Node.js Express.js

**Tools** Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Figma Git Github

Visual Studio Code

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Sr. UI/UX Designer

**OTA World LLC** 

January 2020 – January 2023

Carrollton, Texas

 Led team members to implement product design strategy, and was responsible for improving all design projects by mentoring other designers.

- Applied a human-centered design approach to all parts of the design process, including design research, design thinking, wireframing, prototyping, and visual design.
- Designed user interfaces from concept to finished product for web-based platforms including desktop, tablet, and mobile.
- Developed front-end products using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and delivered products to clients and over 100+ merchants for e-commerce marketing.
- Solved complex design problems using a mobile-first approach, responsive design practices, and testing techniques (A/B, usability, accessibility).
- Communicated project status with owners and stakeholders to ensure alignment with business requirements and project goals.
- Maintained a comprehensive style guide, visual components, typography, and code assets.
- Managed projects in an agile environment to ensure on-time delivery to clients.

#### Visual Designer / Part-time

Binnerri Presbyterian Church

July 2017 - Present Richardson, Texas

- Created all visual assets associated with websites, campaigns, events, and services.
- Took ownership of all projects from concept through to completion and provide creative ideas to solve complex design problems.
- Designed brand identity, typography, color, layouts, graphics, digital and print design.
- Collaborated closely with church leaders to create design solutions that deliver high-quality creative content to over 400+ audiences across the organization.
- Worked in a time-sensitive environment across multiple projects.

#### **Graphic Designer**

PIN Design Inc.

Dallas, Texas

January 2017 - October 2017

- Conceptualized, designed, and implemented creative graphics and content, including branding logos, illustrations, print materials, and digital media.
- Designed user interface (UI) for custom websites, including site mapping, and prototyping.
- Built websites using a web content management system and platform (WordPress, Shopify) and customized layouts and styles by using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Collaborated directly with an art director as a business owner to establish a brand identity and cohesive visual style for each project.
- Worked under tight deadlines and handled a wide variety of projects.

# **Graphic Designer**

Ravis's Ware House

January 2014 – December 2014 Dallas, Texas

- Created print materials to support corporate marketing and promote products and features.
- Refined imagery, typography, and layouts for graphics and digital media.
- Designed within existing visual guidelines to create compelling and brand-centric design solutions.
- Worked directly with stakeholders to align business needs, design concepts, iterate design content with feedback, and deliver the final projects.

## **Product Designer** / Internship

Pantech Wireless, Inc.

January 2010 – January 2011 Seoul, South Korea

- Executed all phases of the mobile design process from concept to highly polished design mockups.
- Practiced user-centered design methods, including user research, personas, user journey maps, storyboards, user flows, wireframes, and prototypes.
- Collaborated closely with managers and fellow designers to refine and improve ideas, communicate design decisions, and execute the product development process.
- Integrated design components to contribute to design systems.

# **EDUCATION**

University of North Texas2020 – 2022M.A. in Interaction DesignDenton, Texas

Southern Methodist University2017 - 2019B.F.A. in Art & Graphic DesignDallas, Texas

B.F.A. in Art & Graphic Design

Dallas, Texas

**Brookhaven College**2014 – 2017

A.A. in General Studies

Farmers Branch, Texas

Christian For The Nations Institute2012 - 2013Accredited Theological DegreeDallas, Texas

Hongik University2006 – 2010B.A. in Product DesignSejong, South Korea